# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name : Teja Wulan

Place, Date of Birth: Tangerang, May 11st, 1998

Sex : Female Marital Status : Single

Height, Weight : 150 cm, 41 kg

Address Sukamantri street, Cilongok RT 02 RW 05 Sukamantri

· Village Pasar Kemis Distric Tangerang Regency

Motto : Work with all your heart and enjoy then you will be optimal

LinkedIn : linkedin.com/in/teja-wulan-8673a6237

## **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

## S1 Electrical Engineering (2016-2021)

Siliwangi University, Tasikmalaya, West Java

GPA : 3.45 of 4.00 Concentration : Material Electric

Final Project : Arduino Based Potentiostat Design for Electrochemical Testing

## **CAREER MAIN ROLE**

I have higly motivation as Electrical Engineer and other position which suitable with my skill and experience. I am meticulous person, collaborative, innovative, working with people, and technology adaption I can also speak English well.

# **CAREER SUMMARY**

Become a back-end software engineer from July 2022 - now at PT. Wide Technologies Indonesia. Logical thinking and problem solving. Proficient in Java programming. I have internship experience at PT. Starcom Solusindo with responsibility for checking IT components such as IDU, ODU, PoE, Subscribes Station, and conducting maintenance on these components and APS Power Supply. I have a Java Programming Course-Net training certificate from Prakerja and simple building installations issued by KEMNAKER, education and training on low voltage installations from PPSDM KEBTKE of the Ministry of Energy and Mineral Resources, Build a website using wordpress from Coursera Network, Google Digital Interpreneurship program from Google and KOMINFO.and lastly, Digital Skill Assessment from the Ministry of BUMN and Indonesia Digital Tribe. I was once the Vice Chairman of the Shihonbu (Japanese Club).

# **CORE COMPETENCE**

- Think analytically and focus on the target
- Detail Oriented and follow the work steps
- Troubleshooter from work constrainct
- Can copywriting well on media or websites
- Can work with a team

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

• Back-end Software Engineer (July 2022-now)

Knowledge of Java and HTML programming logic. Full Stack develops clean code applications for developers. At work, I can use GIT to push code and use the API for testing applications and fixing bugs

Admin and Electrical Maintenance at PT Starcom Solusindo (2019)

Trained to make report on surveys and installations, SPK (Work Order), recapitulation and also to make a project budget and I also worked and helped checking IT items such as IDU, ODU, PoE, Subscriber Station and also maintain APS Power supply. In my internship experience as an admin, I was able to find out the steps in ordering a WiMAX installation service. Then as a maintenance engineer I can know how to maintain all IT components related to WiMAX.

Email: tejawulan8@gmail.com WhatsApp: wa.me/6285648671280 Handphone: +6285648671280

## PROJECT EXPERIENCE

# • Arduino Based Potentiostat Design for Electrochemical Testing

From this final project I understand and pass the device work concept design stage, literature study then after this final project I understand and pass the device work concept design stage, literature study then after that I make a device circuit design, device build, device test by testing trial-error, analysis and then make a report. The device uses an LM324 op-amp with positive and negative power supplies so that the potentiostat produces positive and negative power output sweeps. In this research I have succeeded in making an Arduino-based

# Arduino Based Anti-Flood Pump

In the IoT competition, I participated in the PAB team (anti-flood pump) which was held by the Electrical Student Association of Siliwangi University. Here I and my team use the ultrasonic sensor HC-SR04 and Automatic Water Pump Pressure Sensor Ht60 220 volt 60 watt in the system it works.

#### **SKILL**

- Software
  - Arduino IDE
    Autocad
    DiaLUX
    Ms. Excel
    IntelijIDE
    GIT
    Fritzing
    PLC

- Ms. PowerpointMs. Word
- LabVIEW
  Proteus

- Language Proficiency
  - Bahasa Indonesia
  - English

#### **ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCES**

## • Vice Chairman at Shihonbu /Japanese Club (2017)

Introducing the club to students, registering members, making a schedule for learning Japanese and drawing animanga. here I train communication skills and work together with each other then participate in developing their own talents and their talents as members of the Shihonbu (Japanese Club).

## **COMPETENCE CERTIFICATION**

• Digital Skill Assessment as "Hipster" (2021)

Held by BUMN and Indonesia Digital Tribe

• Intermediate Executor, Low Voltage Electricity Utilization Installation (2020)

Held by The Ministry of Energy and Mineral Resources (ESDM)

## TRAINING CERTIFICATION

• Designing websites with maximizing features on wordpress.

Held by Coursera Network

• Google Digital Interpreneurship (2021)

Held by the Ministry of Communication and Informatics (KOMINFO)

• Installation of Simple Building Installations (2021)

Held by The Ministry of Manpower (KEMNAKER).

# **PERSONALITY**

- In time
- Discipline
- Collaborative
- Honest
- Loyal

## **HOBBIES**

Email: tejawulan8@gmail.com WhatsApp: wa.me/6285648671280 Handphone: +6285648671280

- Reading a Novel and ComicSingingYoga

Email: tejawulan8@gmail.com WhatsApp: wa.me/6285648671280 Handphone: +6285648671280